Guide to the Stanford University, Centennial Office, Records
Stanford University Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1991-183
  - Project and Proposal Files, Subseries 2
    - Jasper Ridge History [includes book by Dorothy F. Regnery, a centennial publication of the Stanford Historical Society] (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Jewish Law: Law in Context and History 1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Library Exhibit on Science (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Library Treasures Exhibit (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Making History Again/Veriation Films 1987 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Master Drawings - Museum Catalog 1988-89 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Mechem Opera 1987 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Mission Mass 1991 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Modernismo (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Modernity in the Middle Ages (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Mozart Colloquium (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Montage [student journal] 1990 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Multicultural celebrations (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Multiculturalism and Institutions (DES) (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Museum Centennial Handbook (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Music Department Commissions 1987-1991 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2011-048
  - Publications Supporting the Featured Objectives of the Stanford Centennial Campaign [list and examples] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Campaign additional publications (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Campaign Honor Roll (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Convocation programs, etc. 1991 Sept. 29 - Oct. 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Cornerstone Celebration programs, etc. 1987 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Centennial miscellany, on campus (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Centennial miscellany, off campus (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Year Founders’ Day programs, etc. 1991 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Year Opening Convocation programs, etc. 1990 Sept. 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Finale Weekend packet, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Finale Weekend program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Finale Weekend registration materials 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Finale Weekend Stadium Spectacular program 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Finale Weekend badges and miscellany 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gold Spike Celebration 1991 May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Letters from school children after talk by Fred Glover on Stanford history, 1991 March (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Postcard Set of Muybridge images of the Stanford’s Nob Hill mansion, commemorating the presentation of the Founding Grant to the Board of Trustees (1885), 1985 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Press clippings, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Symphony event in honor of Stanford Centennial 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Stanford 100 Years of Achievement; Special Centennial Edition of Stanford Magazine, 1991 September (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Centennial News releases 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Songs [1919], Centennial Facsimile Edition, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sun visor "Stanford 100 Years" (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Original newspapers with sections on Centennial events and Stanford history. (Box 3)
- Additional Records, 1985-1991; Accession ARCH-2014-031 (Box 23)
  - Photographs of Leland & Jane Stanford's Nob Hill Mansion, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Five enveloped groups of photographs with description on the outside and the Stanford seal
  - The Human Genome Project: Biological Nature and Social Oppertunities, 1991 Jan 11-13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Program for the events for the Human Genome Project
  - Stanford Court Hotel Event, 1985 Nov 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Invitations and Programs for the Stanford Court Hotel event for the Stanford Centennial Celebration
  - Red Barn Renovation Celebration, 1985 Oct 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Flyers and invitations for the Red Barn Celebration
  - Fourding, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Plans made by the Centennial Committee and other important papers
  - Photos, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Protest Flyers for "Stanford Out of South Africa", 1985 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Text of Speeches: M. Doyle, F. Rhodes, & D. Fehrenbacker, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Copies of Speeches made by M. Doyle, F. Rhodes, & D. Fehrenbacker during the Stanford Centennial Celebration
  - Stanford: A Centennial Chronology Newspaper, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Several newspapers covering the Stanford Centennial Celebration
  - Centennial Activities, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Inivitations, Newspapers, etc. about the activities for the Stanford Centennial Celebration
- Audiovisual material, Accession ARCH-2015-137
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration 'Close", H3; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration 'Close", H4; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Los Angeles - National Centennial Celebration "Speaking of Stanford" TBT - 18:50, H5; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - K-RON Film Speaking of Stanford, H6; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - LA National centennial "speaking of Stanford", H7; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Portland Stanford Centennial Celebration, H8; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Stanford University Seattle Film, H9; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Portland Stanford Centennial Celebration, H10; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Portland Stanford Centennial Celebration, H11; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Special Trustees Centennial Kickoff Meeting. Hoover House, Stanford University 33:30, 1986-12-09; G1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford's Centennial Celebration Century City, G2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - National Centennial Campaign: In Seattle Six Personality Profiles, G3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Bennett Pictres Los Angeles-National Centennial "speaking of Stanford" TRT 18:50, G4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Centennial Campaign Anouncement Channel 7 news coverage, G5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration San Francisco 25:45 MIN, 1988-05-05; G6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Sat Show Professionals LA NCC, G8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - NCC- LA Saturday Professional Cast, G9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Making History Again... Stanford Centennial Cornerstone Celebration, G10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - One Hundred Cardinal Years Newport Beach, Le Medidien Hotel VHS Dub, 1990-09-19; G11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration Century City, G12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University National Centennial Celebration, 1989-12-01; G13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Transcript - Long Version S.F. Cent. R1, G14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration San Francisco 25:45 MIN, 1988-05-05; G15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration - NCC San Diego Student Cast for both shows, 1989-12; G16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Excerpt from Gorbachev's Visit to Stanford: Memorial Auditorium Address, G17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Fairmont Part 2 - Sat Cut 5 17:43, G21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Fairmont Dub of Cut 4, G22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - M/K Show LA Professional Actor Reception Show, G23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - NCC Training Tape Edwards and Crew, G24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)